codexcoder.com 2019-05-07

# Privacy Policy | CodexCoder

CodexCoder values more for your privacy and security information that you share with us via CodexCoder. We become pleased if you feel pleasant to use our site. It is essential to make you inform how we collect, use, maintain, and retain your data. Our privacy policy only collects your personal identification. We do not use this privacy policy for other entities that are not owned, or controlled by our agents, or employees. Requested to take a view on the below privacy policy.

##### Types of Information We Collect

Generally, we collect two types of information:

**Personal Information:** Your name, address, e-mail address, URL, telephone number, account username and password, credit/debit card numbers and associated billing addresses and expiration dates, account numbers and other similar information. That kind of information is only collected if you submit it willingly.

**Non-personal Information:** We collect some analytical and statistical information based on aggregate like other websites. We do not use this non-personal information to contact or identify you. These data are demographic information, user IP addresses, browser types and other anonymous statistical data related to the use of our website.

##### How We Use Your Information

CodexCoder may use and disclose your information as the rule of this privacy policy. Besides the rule of this privacy policy, any other purposes of information are- order fulfillment and administration, product surveys, billing audits and other similar uses. If the situation is reasonable, we only collect, use and disclose your personal or non-personal information. To use your data, we only use the lawful fair ways. We reserve the right to use or disclose the aggregated information and business contact information in the ways that are appropriate.

##### Children Awareness

We do not allow the people who are thirteen or under thirteen to become our member and we discourage them to share their personal information with us.

##### Web Cookies/Tracking Technology

CodexCoder may use cookies. A cookie is a small data file sent to the visitors PC that identifies his/her computer to a specific web site. A cookie will not provide any personally identifiable information about visitor, nor will it read data off of any visitor’s hard disk, or read cookie files created by other websites.

CodexCoder uses the information provided by a cookie for targeting of advertising and tracking site usage. This allows CodexCoder to customize your visit and save you time during next visits.

**Sharing of Information Collected by CodexCoder:** CodexCoder does not share or exchange the personal information of our PAID SERVICES customers with third parties without the specific permission of the customer.

##### Other Website Links

When you click on a link on our website, you may be taken into another website operated by different companies. You are subject to obey that company’s privacy policy.

##### Storage and Security

All kinds of data collected by CodexCoder is stored in secure servers located in the USA. CodexCoder has security systems in place to defend the loss, misuse or alteration of information under its control. Here these security systems include the essential shield to prevent, as far as possible, access to CodexCoder databases to parties other than CodexCoder. The extreme care is well-kept to ensure your personal information is not at any risk.

##### Contact Information

If you have any question about this privacy policy or our site, requested feel free to contact with us by support@codexcoder.com email address.

##### Information Update

You reserve the right to change or update your personal data if needed. Just login to our site to correct your personal information.
